Trevor Bruce

Savvy, Energetic & Driven Team Player with Four Years IT Support Experience

Denver, CO 80209 tbnyk03@gmail.com (720)487-5026

IT Support Specialist experienced in successful troubleshooting and terrific interpersonal skills in resolving issues for end user's in an efficient manner. Possesses thorough knowledge of computer hardware and software applications. Proven ability to adapt to changing trends and a strong dedication to continue learning emerging technologies.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Software Support Specialist

Sentinel Systems - Denver, CO February 2021 to Present

Provide support to users of our software in a timely and efficient manner using an incoming ticketing system.

Address a wide range of customer issues relating to the performance and usage of our self-storage software.

Perform installs and upgrades for our customers.

IT Manager

Flatirons Subaru - Boulder, CO 2016 to 2020

Implemented and oversaw a system for managing over 100 end devices (PC's, smartphones, printers, etc.) in a high volume work environment

- Mitigated spam e-mail through the implementation of Barracuda Networks E-Mail Security
- Installed and managed VoIP phone system across multiple departments and end users
- Integral in deploying and educating employees across multiple departments on new DMS software to increase productivity and work flow
- Diagnose and resolve various hardware and network issues for end users, patiently and in a timely manner
- Proven ability to work with team members from all departments within the company to increase communication and productivity amongst departments.
- Oversaw the installation of anti-virus programs for users and the removal of viruses.

Education

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE in Communications and Media Production

State University of New York - Brockport, NY

January 2010 to December 2013

Skills

- Network Administration
- IT Management
- Exchange
- VolP
- Zendesk

Additional Information

- Proficient in Editing software (FinalCut Pro, Adobe Premier)
- Proficient in Photoshop and Adobe After Effects
- Experience working on various video shoots with a wide array of team members
- Ability to work in high-pressure environment
- Excellent communication skills
- Excellent Team Player